Guide to the Vassar College Buildings and Grounds Files, 1879-2007 (bulk 1910-2000)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- [Blodgett VII], 1997 (Box 50)
- [Blodgett VII], 1998 (Box 50)
- [Construction Meeting 3], 1998 (Box 51)
- [Blodgett Hall Audio-Visual], 1997 (Box 51)
- [Blodgett Hall A.V Report, (J. Gray Copy)], 1999 (Box 51)
- [Blodgett Hall Construction Minutes], 1996-1998 (Box 51)
- [Blodgett Hall – F.F. and E Purchases], 1998 (Box 51)
- [Blodgett Hall Landscaping, Endowment Plan and Laboratory Animal Guide], 1994 (Box 51)
- [Loeb Art Center Contract Bids], 1991 (Box 51)
- [Guard Booth, Vassar College – Project Manual], 1993 (Box 51)
- Studio Arts, 1991-1994 (Box 51)
- Closeout, 1993-1994 (Box 51)
- Punch List, 1993 (Box 51)
- Studio Arts Meeting Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 52)
- ICC Rebate, 1994 (Box 52)
- Corr. Building Permit, 1990-1994 (Box 52)
- Studio Arts Corr. Michael Bocanos Project Manager, 1992-1994 (Box 52)
- Studio Arts Corr. Vassar College (Misc), 1993 (Box 52)
- Studio Arts Corr. A Stellato, 1991-1993 (Box 52)
- Studio Arts Transmittals, 1992-1993 (Box 52)
- Ceramics Workshop, 1992-1993 (Box 52)
- Studio Arts Correspondence, 1990 -1994; (3 folders) (Box 52)
- Studio Arts Design Notes/Schemes, 1992-1994 (Box 52)
- FF and E, 1992-1993 (Box 52)
- Studio Arts Site Plans Info, 1992 (Box 52)
- Signage, 1992 (Box 52)
- Vassar Attan Res., 1976 (Box 52)
- Vassar Dining Hall, 1973 (Box 52)
- Vassar College – Food Service Equipment, 1959-1963; (2 folders) (Box 52)
- Vassar College Access For Handicapped – All Correspondence (Except Contractors), 1978-1971 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Ramp For Main Building – Job Reports, 1979 (Box 52)
- Vassar Access/Handicapped Report, 1978 (Box 52)
- Vassar Access Ramp/Lockwood Library Specifications, 1979 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Ramp For Lockwood Library – Job Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 52)
- Vassar Access Ramp/Main Building Specifications (Box 52)
- Vassar Handrails All Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 52)
- Vassar Kenyon Gym – Main Entrance Doors All Correspondence, 1979 (Box 52)
- Vassar Townhouse Laundry Building All Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Laundry Building Specifications, 1972-1973 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Laundry Building Eberhard Builders, Inc., 1973 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Library Extension Program Requirements, 1959 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Library Extension Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson and Abbott, Architects, 1959-1963 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Library Expansion Reports, 1960 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Library Extension Owner Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Library Extension Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Library Expansion – Budgets, 1961 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Library Expansion – Clarke and Rapuano, 1960 (Box 52)
- Vassar Library and Taylor Hall – Miscellaneous Hand-written Notes, 1979 (Box 52)
- Vassar College Master Plan Owner’s Correspondence, 1959-1973 (Box 52)
- Vassar Mehaffey Res., 1977 (Box 53)
- Vassar College Consultation – Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 53)
- Vassar (Consulting) Quadrangle/Dorms, 1965-1969 (Box 53)
- Vassar, 1976-1977 (Box 53)
- Vassar – Minutes Master Plan Comm., 1974-1977 (Box 53)
- Vassar College Consultation Proposed New Theatre, 1965-1971 (Box 53)
- Vassar Consultation, 1964-1975; (12 folders) (Box 53)
- Vassar Consultation Preliminary Traffic Plan, 1972 (Box 53)
- Vassar College Chapel Consultation, 1963-1967 (Box 53)
- Vassar Master Plan Wilbur Smith and Associates, 1971-1973 (Box 53)
- Vassar College Alterations To Chicago Hall – Idema General Contractors, 1979-1980 (Box 53)
- Misc. Drawings, 1970 (Box 53)
- Vassar College Preliminary Traffic Plan, 1972 (Box 53)
- Prior To 64, 1959-1962 (Box 53)
- Vassar College Head House At Skinner Greenhouse All Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 53)
- Vassar College Engineering Survey Consultation, 1966 (Box 53)
- Vassar College Consultation – John M. Johansen and Associates Architects, 1965-1968 (Box 53)
- Vassar College Consultation Job Reports, 1965 (Box 53)
- Vassar College Science Consultation, 1965-1970 (Box 53)
- Vassar College Goldstone and Dearborn Quadrangle, 1964-1966 (Box 53)
- Vassar – Biological Science Building, 1968 (Box 53)
- Vassar Master Plan – Draft Copies, 1969 (Box 54)
- Vassar – Main Building, Avery, Blodgett and Skinner Halls Alterations Owner Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 54)
- Vassar – Main Building, Avery, Blodgett and Skinner Hall Alterations Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980 (Box 54)
- Vassar – Main Building, Avery, Blodgett and Skinner Halls Alterations Job Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 54)
- Vassar – Main Building, Avery, Blodgett and Skinner Halls, Alterations Conference Reports, 1980 (Box 54)
- Vassar – Main Building, Avery, Blodgett and Skinner Halls, Alterations Specifications, 1979-1980 (Box 54)
- Vassar – Main Building, Avery, Blodgett and Skinner Hall, Alterations Bidders, 1980 (Box 54)
- Alterations To Third Fl. Baldwin Hall Vassar College – Idema Correspondence, 1980 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Mab and S Alterations– Idema General Contract Documents, 1980 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Mab and S Alterations– Idema General Contractors Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 54)
- Mehaffey Residence Vassar College All Correspondence, 1977 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Head House At Skinner Greenhouses Documents, 1984 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Head House At Skinner Greenhouses Conference Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Head House At Skinner Greenhouses Job Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Head House At Skinner Greenhouses Specifications, 1983 (Box 54)
- Phys. Ed. Facilities Study All Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 54)
- Vassar – Phys. Ed. Facilities Report, 1977-1979 (Box 54)
- Vassar – Faculty Housing Site Studies, 1969 (Box 54)
- Vassar – Academic Space Requirements Administrative Space, 1971 (Box 54)
- Vassar Poughkeepsie Day School – Program Requirements (Box 54)
- Vassar Poughkeepsie Day School – William E. Gindle Architect, 1962-1963 (Box 54)
- Vassar Poughkeepsie Day School – Gordon S. Marvel Architect, 1962 (Box 54)
- Vassar Poughkeepsie Day School – Owner Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 54)
- Vassar Poughkeepsie Day School – Conference Reports, 1962 (Box 54)
- Vassar Poughkeepsie Day School – Specifications, 1963 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Type “C” Owner Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Type “C” Budgets/Estimates, 1968-1969 (Box 54)
- Vassar Student Housing. Agreements and Statements, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Type “C” Clerk-Of-The-Works, 1971 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Type “C’ Eberhard Builders, Inc. Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Type “C” Job Reports, 1971 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Type “C” Conference Reports, 1971 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Type “C’ Milton Chazen Assoc, 1971 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Type “C” James Kennedy, 1971 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Type “C” Eberhard Builders, Inc. Documents, 1971 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Special Orders, 1971 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Type “C”, 1971 (Box 54)
- Vassar College – Taylor Hall Budgets, 1960 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Taylor Hall – Program Requirements, 1959 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Taylor Hall – Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson and Abbott, 1960-1963 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Taylor Hall – Owner’s Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Alumnae House Correspondence, 1966 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Taylor Hall – Conference Reports, 1962 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Taylor Hall – Clarke and Rapuano, Inc., 1963 (Box 54)
- Vietor, Mrs. Thomas Invoices, 1967 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Student Housing Type “C” Specifications, 1971 (Box 54)
- Vassar College – Martin Place, 1988 (Box 54)
- Vassar – Basement Lang. Lab. Contractor’s Correspondence, 1987-1988; (2 folders) (Box 54)
- Vassar College – Job Reports Language Lab. Phase II – Chicago Hall, 1988 (Box 54)
- Vassar College – Language Lab. – Phase II Specifications, 1987 (Box 54)
- Vassar College – Conference Report Basement Floor – Language Laboratory, 1987 (Box 54)
- Vassar College – Language Lab – Phase II Idema Documents, 1987-1988 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Chicago Hall Contractor’s Correspondence, 1986 (Box 54)
- [Chicago Hall Alteration Specs (Office Copy)], 1979 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Chicago Language Lab Conference Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Chicago Language Lab All Correspond., 1984-1987 (Box 54)
- Specifications Vassar College Language Laboratory, 1985 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Chicago Language Lab Job Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 54)
- Vassar College - Specifications Office Rehabilitation, 1986 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Office Rehabs. Job Reports, 1986 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Office Rehabs. Matthew Idema Documents, 1989 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Office Rehabs. All Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 54)
- Vassar College – Facilities Operation All Correspondence, 1989 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Antolini Residence – Cubages and Estimates, 1959 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Antolini Residence – Program Requirements (Box 54)
- Vassar College Antolini Residence – Owner Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Antolini Residence – Reports, 1959 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Antolini Residence – Specifications, 1959 (Box 54)
- Vassar Athletic Fields, 1974 (Box 54)
- Vassar Athletic Fields Spoor-Lasher Co. Corres. – Documents, 1974 (Box 54)
- Vassar Athletic Fields Specifications, 1974 (Box 54)
- Alterations To Third Fl. Baldwin Hall Vassar College – Owner Correspondence, 1980 (Box 54)
- Alterations To Third Fl. Baldwin Hall Vassar College Job Reports, 1980 (Box 54)
- Alterations To Third Fl. Baldwin Hall Vassar College – Idema Documents, 1980 (Box 54)
- Alterations To Third Fl. Baldwin Hall Vassar College – Misc. Correspondence, 1989 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Book Store – Dawson, Oliver and Murtagh, Archs., 1960 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Book Store – Owner Correspondence, 1960 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Campus Develop. Agreements and Statements, 1959-1964 (Box 54)
- Vassar Dorm Survey Agreements and Statements, 1968-1979 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Campus Develop. Conference Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 54)
- Vassar General – Miscellaneous Hand-written Notes, Etc., 1964 (Box 54)
- Vassar College Campus Development – Architects and Consultants, 1960-1963 (Box 54)
- Vassar Sanders/Elevator Specifications, 1977 (Box 54)
- Vassar – Chem. Building Elevator, 1976 (Box 54)
- Vassar Chemistry Building Safety Rehab All Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 55)
- Vassar Chemistry Building Expansion All Correspondence, 1978 (Box 55)
- Vassar Sanders Chem. Building Conference Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 55)
- Vassar College – Chicago Hall Alterations Job Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Chicago Hall Alterations– Specifications, 1979 (Box 55)
- [Specifications For Alumnae House Alteration], 1982 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Alumnae House Conference Reports, 1981 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Alumnae House Job Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Alumnae House Documents, 1982-1983 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Chicago Hall Documents, 1985-1986 (Box 55)
- Vassar College – Acoustics All Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Consultation Master Plan, 1976 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Master Plan Conference Reports, 1972, 1975 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Acoustics – Conference Reports, 1980 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Acoustics – Special Orders, 1980-1981 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Art Department – All Correspondence, 1979 (Box 55)
- [Survey Of Existing Dormitory Facilities And Recommended Modernization], 1968 (Box 55)
- [Vassar – Kendrick], 1975-1976 (Box 55)
- Vassar Wilbur Smith – Packing Study, 1971 (Box 55)
- Vassar Athletic Fields Agreements and Statements, 1974-1975 (Box 55)
- Vassar – Athletic Fields, 1973-1974 (Box 55)
- Vassar, 1973-1974 (Box 55)
- Vassar Prentiss Field, 1974 (Box 55)
- Vassar Avery, 1976 (Box 55)
- Vassar – Students’ Building – Snack Bar Owner Correspondence, 1960 (Box 55)
- Vassar – Students’ Building – Snack Bar Brownjohn, Chermayeff and Geismar, 1960 (Box 55)
- Vassar Sanders Chem. Building Special Study All Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 55)
- Vassar Sanders Chem. Building Special Study Report, 1976-1978 (Box 55)
- Vassar Sanders Chem. Rehab. Meyer, Strong and Jones, 1978 (Box 55)
- Vassar Chem. Safety Rehab. Job Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Alterations To Computer Center All Correspond., 1984-1985 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Alterations To Computer Center Specifications, 1984 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Alterations To Computer Center Documents, 1978. 1984, 1986 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Rockefeller Hall Alterations– Conference Reports, 1980 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Ramp For Main Building – Matthew Idema Documents and Correspondence, 1979 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Ramp For Lockwood Library – Manfredi Construction Documents and Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Elevator For Rockefeller Hall – Otis Elevators Documents and Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Rockefeller Hall Alterations – Manfredi Const. Documents and Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Rockefeller Hall Alterations – Job Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 55)
- Vassar Access Rockefeller Hall Specifications, 1979 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Computer Rises All Correspondence, 1983 (Box 55)
- [Vassar Dormitory Rehabilitation Study], 1972 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Faculty Housing Carl Koch and Assoc. Architects, 1965-1966 (Box 55)
- Vassar Spicer House, 1975 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Parrish House (All Correspondence), 1967 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Faculty Housing Owner Correspondence, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1963, 1965, 1966 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Faculty Housing – Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1965 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Faculty Housing – Clarke and Rapuano, 1960-1963 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Alumnae House, 1982 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Antennas, 1985 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Avery, 1989 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Athletic Field, 1973-1974 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Facilities Offices, 1988 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Blodgett, 1989 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Baldwin, 1980 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Computer Center, 1984 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Exterior Railings, 1978 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Cushing, 1989 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Animal Facilities Blodgett, 1990 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Chapel, 1984 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Facilities Rehab, 1990 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Ferry House, 1987 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Head House @ Skinner GRNHSE, 1984 (Box 55)
- Vassar College ICC 6 College Activities, 1989 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Jewett, 1979 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Kenyon Gym, 1986 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Kenyon Entrance, 1979 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Phase II Language Lab, 1987 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Laundry At Town Houses, 1972-1973 (Box 55)
- Lockwood and Thompson Vassar College, 1979 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Ramps Chicago Hall Computer Center Lockwood Library, 1980 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Mabs, 1980 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Ramp For Main Building (Box 55)
- Vassar College Mudd Chemistry, 1988 -1989; (2 folders) (Box 55)
- Vassar College New England, 1990 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Olmsted, 1981 (Box 55)
- Vassar College President’s House, 1986 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Powerhouse Theater, 1990 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Sanders, 1977-1978 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Sanders 200 Drawings, 1988 (Box 55)
- Vassar College Sanders Furnishings, 1989 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Sanders Classroom 200 Drawings, 1988 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Skinner Parking, 1972 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Torch and Owl, 1985 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Sun Dial (Box 56)
- Vassar College Swift and Metcalf, 1987 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Misc Toilets, 1986, 1990 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Town Houses, 1975, 1986 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Main Miscellaneous, 1969, 1976, 1985 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Main Hall Owner Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Main Hall Miscellaneous, 1960, 1962 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Main Hall Campbell Building Co., General Contractor, 1959 (Box 56)
- Vassar College 2nd Floor Main, 1985-1986 (Box 56)
- Vassar College First Floor Main, 1985, 1987 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Juice Bar Proposal, 1986 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Rockefeller Hall, 1979-1980; (2 folders) (Box 56)
- Vassar College Skinner Hall, 1980 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Taylor, 1979 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Vassar Farm Bridge, 1990 (Box 56)
- Vassar College New England BSMT Spec., 1990 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Alumnae Ramp Specifications, 1990 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Alumnae House Rump All Correspondence, 1990 (Box 56)
- Vassar New England Manfredi Documents, 1990 (Box 56)
- Vassar New England Job and Conference Reports, 1990 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Blodgett Animal Facility, 1990 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Wimpfheimer Nursery School, 1986, 1990, 1991 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Powerhouse Theater, 1990 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Misc. Correspondence, 1962-1990; (3 folders) (Box 56)
- Vassar New England All Correspondence, 1990 (Box 56)
- Sanders Classroom - Owners Correspondence, 1990 (Box 56)
- Sanders Classroom - Idema Documents, 1988 (Box 56)
- Sanders Classroom – Vassar College Contractor’s Correspondence, 1988-1990; (2 folders) (Box 56)
- Vassar College – Sanders Classroom Job Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 56)
- Sanders Classroom - Bidders, 1987 (Box 56)
- Sanders Classroom - Addendum, 1987 (Box 56)
- Sanders Classroom - Conference Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Office Rehabs. Bidders Correspondence, 1987 (Box 56)
- Sanders Classroom - Addendum No 1, 1987 (Box 56)
- Sanders Classroom – Furnishings, 1988 (Box 56)
- Sanders Classroom - Preliminary Design Report, 1987 (Box 56)
- Sanders Classroom - Edwards and Zuck, 1987-1989 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Alt/Ren. Alumnae House All Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 56)
- Vassar College Main Hall Goldstone and Dearborn, Architects, 1959-1960; (2 folders) (Box 57)
- Vassar College Main Hall – Conference Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 57)
- Vassar College Main Hall Clarke and Rapuano Landscape Arch., 1959, 1960, 1967 (Box 57)
- Wooster School – Chapel and Honor Room Specifications, 1962 (Box 57)
- Mudd Mechanical Repair [Bills], 1988-1989 (Box 57)
- Sanders Classroom [Bills and Invoices], 1989 (Box 57)
- [Asbestos Abatement], 1984 (Box 57)
- [Mudd Mechanical Upgrade- Work Requests and Invoices], 1989 (Box 57)
- [Raymond House Electrical Upgrade – Work Requests, Invoices and Specifications], 1989 (Box 57)
- [ACDC Waste Pumping System Orders], 1987-1988 (Box 57)
- [Alarm and Security System Payments], 1987-1988 (Box 57)
- Lathrop House Fire Alarm and Electrical System Upgrade [Work Requests and Invoices], 1987-1989 (Box 57)
- [Electrical Distribution System Upgrade – Work Requests and Invoices], 1987-1988 (Box 57)
- [College and Raymond Ave. Asbestos Abatement], 1987 (Box 57)
- Retreat, 1988-1989 (Box 57)
- Signage, 1986, 1987, 1990 (Box 57)
- Interior Signage, 1987 (Box 57)
- Campus – Signage, 1987-1988 (Box 57)
- Rewire Raymond Hall, 1989-1990; (2 folders) (Box 57)
- Mudd Upgrade Mechanical, 1987-1990 (Box 57)
- Mudd Chemistry Building Punchlist, 1989-1990 (Box 57)
- Raymond Bathroom Upgrade (Box 57)
- Asbestos Management, 1989 (Box 57)
- Letters Of Notification, 1989 (Box 57)
- Avery Upgrade Offices (Box 57)
- Technical Specifications – Rockefeller Hall Roof Repair and Installation Contract, 1989 (Box 57)
- Town House Boiler Replacement, 1989 (Box 57)
- Rombout Porch Pillar Replacement, 1989 (Box 57)
- Avery Hall Roof Replacement, 1989 (Box 57)
- Kenyon Roof Replacement, 1989 (Box 57)
- Central Heating Plant Boiler Replacement, 1988-1990 (Box 57)
- [Boiler Room Repairs, Invoices, Time Sheets and Work Orders], 1989-1990 (Box 58)
- Williams Plumbing Replacement, 1990 (Box 58)
- Terrace Apartments Heating Upgrade, 1989 (Box 58)
- Main Rezone Housefellows [Work Orders], 1989 (Box 58)
- Davison Energy Management, 1989 (Box 58)
- Raymond Hall Energy Management, 1989 (Box 58)
- North Gate Parking Lot, 1989 (Box 58)
- North Lot Rebuilding [Correspondence, Specifications and Permits], 1989 (Box 58)
- Blodgett Wiring Upgrade, 1989 (Box 58)
- Rockefeller Wiring Upgrade, 1989 (Box 58)
- Rekey Raymond [Work Orders], 1989 (Box 58)
- Campus Emergency Lighting [Work Orders], 1989 (Box 58)
- ACDC Upgrade Foyer [Work Orders, Invoices, Drawings and Plans], 1989 (Box 58)
- Vassar College Loeb Art Center Record Change Orders, 1992-1993; (2 folders) (Box 58)
- Vassar Alumnae House – Specifications and Plans, 1979, 1982, 1990 (Box 58)
- Specifications and Plans – New England Building, 1990 (Box 58)
- Vassar – Sanders Classroom Building – Folded Plans for Millwork, Ceiling, and Stairs, 1988; (4 folders) (Box 58)
- Main Building Second Floor [Project Submittal and Plans], 1988; (2 folders) (Box 59)
- Chicago Hall - Vassar Language Lab [Proposal and Plans], 1988 (Box 59)
- Head House – Vassar College [Plans and Manuals], 1984 (Box 59)
- Vassar – Miscellaneous Plans, 1979-1980 (Box 59)
- Lockwood Library [Plans for Ramp Railing], 1984 (Box 59)
- Computer Center – Hollow Metal [Submittal Forms], 1984 (Box 59)
- Alumnae Association of Vassar College Addition [Alumnae House Renovations], 1979 (Box 59)
- [Vassar Railings – Specifications and Plans], 1978-1980 (Box 59)
- [Main Building – Ramp Specifications] (Box 59)
- Skinner Hall – Head House Specifications, 1983 (Box 59)
- Computer Center – Specifications for Alterations, 1984 (Box 59)
- Chicago Hall – Specifications for Alterations to the Language Laboratory, 1985, 1987; (2 folders) (Box 59)
- New England Building – Specifications for Alterations to Basement Floor, 1990 (Box 59)
- Main Building – Specifications for Office Rehabilitations and Second Floor, 1986 (Box 59)
- Sanders Chemistry Building – Specifications for Elevator Installation, General Construction and Mechanical Work, 1977, 1987; (3 folders) (Box 59)
- Rockefeller Hall – Specifications for Alterations, 1979 (Box 59)
- Lockwood Library – Specifications for Ramp, 1979 (Box 59)
- Alterations for Main Building, Avery, Blodgett and Skinner Halls, 1980 (Box 59)
- Sanders Classroom Building – Finished Hardware [Correspondence and Schedule], 1988 (Box 59)
- Sanders Classroom Building – Plumbing, HVAC and Sprinkler Shop Drawings, 1989 (Box 59)
- Sanders Classroom – [Plumbing, HVAC and Sprinkler], Shop Drawings, 1988; (2 folders) (Box 60)
- Sanders Classroom – Arch Shop Drawings, 1988 (Box 60)
- Sanders Classroom – Electrical Shop Drawings, 1988 (Box 60)
- Sanders Classroom – 87’-’88, 1987-1988 (Box 60)
- Historic Preservation, 1988 (Box 60)
- Sanders Building – Contract and Job Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 60)
- Sanders ’88 – Punch Lists Classroom, 1989 (Box 60)
- Sanders – Furnishings and Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 60)
- Sanders Classroom Move, 1989 (Box 60)
- Construction Costs, 1987-1989 (Box 60)
- Architectural Fees, 1987-1988 (Box 60)
- Preliminary Expenditures, 1987 (Box 60)
- Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 60)
- Sanders C.O. and Inspection and Guarantees, 1988-1989 (Box 60)
- Sanders – HVAC and Roofing, 1988-1989 (Box 61)
- Sanders – Change Estimates, 1988-1989 (Box 61)
- Alumnae House Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
- Avery Hall Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
- College Center Energy Audit (Box 61)
- Computer Center Energy Audit (Box 61)
- Davison House Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
- Lathrop House Energy Audit (Box 61)
- Main Building Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
- New England ECM [Energy Audit], 1980-1981 (Box 61)
- Raymond House Energy Audit, 1983 (Box 61)
- Sanders Chemistry Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
- Sanders Physics Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
- Strong House Energy Audit (Box 61)
- Non Collusion Affidavit (Box 61)
- Tax Exemption Clause to Accompany Purchase Orders (Box 61)
- Freshman Parent’s Weekend, 1987 (Box 61)
- Heating – Rentals, 1986 (Box 61)